// Questions, Options and correct answer array
let questions=[
    {
        num:1,
        Question: "What is the commercial capital city of Sri Lanka?",
        Answer: "A) Colombo",
        options:[
            "A) Colombo",
            "B) Kandy",
            "C) Galle",
            "D) Kurunagala"
        ]
    },
    {
        num:2,
        Question: "What is the currency of Sri Lanka?",
        Answer: "B) Sri Lankan Rupee",
        options:[ 
            "A) Sri Lankan Dollar",
            "B) Sri Lankan Rupee",
            "C) Sri Lankan Yen",
            "D) Sri Lankan Pound"

        ]
    },
    {
        num:3,
        Question: "What is the name of the ancient rock fortress located in central Sri Lanka?",
        Answer: "A) Sigiriya",
        options:[
            "A) Sigiriya",
            "B) Dambulla",
            "C) Polonnaruwa",
            "D) Yapahuwa"


        ]
    },
    {
        num:4,
        Question: "What is Sri Lanka's highest mountain?",
        Answer: "D) Piduruthalagala",
        options:[
            "A) Mount Everest",
            "B) Grand Teton",
            "C) Mount Kilimanjaro",
            "D) Piduruthalagala"

        ]
    },
    {
        num:5,
        Question: "What animal appears on flag of Sri Lanka?",
        Answer: "C) Lion",
        options:[
            "A) Elephant",
            "B) Peacock",
            "C) Lion",
            "D) Tiger"
            

        ]
    },
    {
        num:6,
        Question: "What is the name of Sri Lanka's famous tea-growing region?",
        Answer: "B) Nuwara Eliya",
        options:[
            "A) Colombo",
            "B) Nuwara Eliya",
            "C) Jaffna",
            "D) Hambanthota"

        ]
    },
    {
        num:7,
        Question: "What among the following is the traditional Sri Lankan greeting?",
        Answer: "D) Ayubowan",
        options:[
            "A) Namasthe",
            "B) Ciao",
            "C) Annyeonghaseyo",
            "D) Ayubowan"

        ]
    },
    {
        num:8,
        Question: "Which ocean surrounds Sri Lanka?",
        Answer: "C) Indian Ocean",
        options:[
            "A) Pacific Ocean",
            "B) Arctic Ocean",
            "C) Indian Ocean",
            "D) Atlantic Ocean"

        ]
    },
    {
        num:9,
        Question: "What is the longest river in Sri Lanka?",
        Answer: "B) Mahawali",
        options:[
            "A) Nile",
            "B) Mahawali",
            "C) Yamuna",
            "D) Kelani"

        ]
    },
    {
        num:10,
        Question: "How was Sri Lanka formerly known?",
        Answer: "A) Ceylon",
        options:[
            "A) Ceylon",
            "B) Burma",
            "C) Formosa",
            "D) Nyasaland"

        ]
    },

]